[
  {
    "questionNo": 1,
    "question": "Who is the main character in the anime 'Naruto'?",
    "options": ["Sasuke Uchiha", "Kakashi Hatake", "Naruto Uzumaki"],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 2,
    "question": "Which anime features a group of pirates searching for the 'One Piece'?",
    "options": ["Attack on Titan", "One Piece", "My Hero Academia"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 3,
    "question": "What is the name of the anime about a young girl and her spirit friend traveling between worlds?",
    "options": ["Spirited Away", "My Neighbor Totoro", "Mushishi"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 4,
    "question": "In 'Dragon Ball Z,' who is known for his iconic 'Kamehameha' energy attack?",
    "options": ["Goku", "Vegeta", "Piccolo"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 5,
    "question": "What is the title of the anime featuring the adventures of Monkey D. Luffy and his crew?",
    "options": ["Bleach", "One Piece", "Naruto"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 6,
    "question": "Which anime is set in the post-apocalyptic world of 'Tokyo-3'?",
    "options": ["Neon Genesis Evangelion", "Cowboy Bebop", "Fullmetal Alchemist"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 7,
    "question": "In 'Death Note,' what object gives its user the power to kill anyone by writing their name in it?",
    "options": ["Sword", "Notebook", "Key"],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 8,
    "question": "What is the name of the demon who serves as a butler to Ciel Phantomhive in 'Black Butler'?",
    "options": ["Sebastian", "Grell", "William"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 9,
    "question": "In 'My Hero Academia,' what is the main character Izuku Midoriya's superhero name?",
    "options": ["Deku", "Shoto", "Bakugo"],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": 10,
    "question": "Which anime features a young alchemist seeking the Philosopher's Stone to restore his brother's body?",
    "options": ["Fullmetal Alchemist", "Attack on Titan", "Demon Slayer"],
    "correctOption": 1
  }
]
